This...
this can't be!
Oh...
I didn't see him with the mask.
I didn't know that he
had it anywhere near him.
I didn't see him put in the red stone.
No, it can't be. Dear God.
Kars.
We will be back in the air,
We will be back in the air.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I think it's a big space.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
You're the one who won't
hit I don't even know?
Oh, God!
You're the one
who
won't win.
You're the one who won the fight!
He'll stood up again, Major!
You're the fatherland's cream of the crop!
You will stand your ground no matter what!
He has become the uber-mensch! Can it be?
I thought no creature could
attain perfection, but now...
Damn you!
See that?
How his arm is burning?
Maybe we don't have to
fight perfection after all!
Harmon melts his accursed flesh even now!
In another minute, there
will be nothing left of him!
He has lusted after the
Red Stone for millennia,
but when it is all said and done,
his quest for immortality has failed!
You will perish knowing
that you are a failure!
Ready the UV amplifier for another shot!
One direct hit should be
enough to finish him off!
Put it up, soldier!
What's he doing?
Looks like he's thinking.
Staring at a damn squirrel. What the hell?
Look, Mr. Speedwagon!
His hand, it's changing!
I've seen some crazy stuff, but this...
Gets his hands on the red stone, first
thing he does is make a squirrel?
Oh, hey, look at that, I
think you found a friend.
Hey, Squirrel, get away from that thing!
You don't know the guy it's made of!
Ha, ha, ha!
Spurly gummy!
Soldiers!
Full retreat!
My god!
He has complete mastery over organic life!
Alright!
The sun is rising!
Not a one of them left alive!
Kars is about to get what's coming to him!
Thank goodness!
Think again!
He's feeling fine!
He's standing in the morning sun!
And he couldn't care less about it!
Jojo!
This is a horrible
nightmare! We're doomed!
This is the day all of us die!
Humanity's done for!
Alpha and Omega both.
I am the pinnacle of all life
that has ever trod the Earth.
All of their forms are mine to take.
And you, my old nemesis, I
see how entrancing you are.
Yours is a beauty the likes
of which I have never seen.
I once feared you, but
now I fear you no more.
Kars, he's become invincible.
He has no weaknesses now.
He even shrugs off
Hamon like it's nothing.
He's won, and he knows it.
You can see it in his eyes.
Cars the pillar man is no more!
He's become Cars the ultimate creation!
This is all my fault.
I'm the one who hit him with the UV
after he put on the completed mask.
Is...
is there really no way to stop him, Mr.
Speedwagon?
He's so strong now!
We're all gonna be food for
this walking museum piece!
Now, I've got a plan, huh?
Did I hear you right, Jojo?
Hold her.
Uh-huh.
One last all-or-nothing gambit!
All-or-nothing gambit, you say?
Yeah, it's my final move.
What does it involve?
Jojo, when you say final move, you're not
referring to that final move, are you?
Listen up!
This is something you're going
to have to do for yourself!
Just tell me what to do and
I'll follow your lead, Jojo!
Run for your life!
Oh, man, I knew you were gonna do that!
Amon users mean nothing to me
now, but you are a special case.
This is a historic moment, and
Wamuu and ACDC must be avenged.
I shall celebrate my rebirth
With the utter eradication
of Joseph Joestar!
He's gaining on us! Not helping!
Really?
How am I going to think of
something with you carrying on?
We've still got our dignity, Smokey!
JoJo's out there risking life and limb
to lead cars away from us. Good on you!
But still, it is only a matter of time.
This foe ain't one you
can beat! He's coming!
If you're gonna think
of something, do it now!
Why are you running with me, anyway?
Maybe you haven't
noticed this yet, Smokey,
but I'm the one who's got Kars
really banked out of shape, you know?
You and I are good friends,
so I'll take it really badly
if you die because of me today!
For the moment, at least,
Kars is after my blood alone.
He thinks that killing means a
good way to wring in his new life,
which means that monster's
not going to stop chasing me?
until I've drawn my final breath!
Jojo, there's something
you really need to know.
Lisa, Lisa, she's more than just
some humble master. She's your...
That was fast.
Quit flapping, you son of a bitch.
Speed wagon, tell me,
has that pillar man really
become a perfect being?
Yes, our greatest fear has been realized.
Right in front of us, Kars has become
an unstoppable force of nature!
A perfect being is above all invincible.
That means it does not grow old.
It will never succumb
to death in any form.
Additionally,
it has the abilities of all other life
forms at its disposal and outperforms them.
And finally,
its predominant form is the standard
by which physical perfection is judged.
We have no way to stop him now.
We've already lost.
He has no weaknesses at all!
Humans can't kill him!
Not even Hamon or the sun itself
will do a lick of good against him!
Jojo!
Sorry, but you're gonna
have to tell me later! Huh?
I'm kinda short on time!
Jojo!
Hm.
That won't save you.
Ha ha!
You're not the only one with wings!
I'm coming for ya!
Up there!
That's one of our German warplanes!
Jojo!
Kars mutates his feathers into
plated projectiles as hard as
armadillo shells and coats them
with a bullet deflecting oil.
Therefore, their toughness makes
them ideal not only as shielding,
but as weapons in their own right.
Shooting those feathers
at me is dirty pool.
This doesn't look good.
Oh, no, you don't.
Touching down is not an option.
I've got to make my getaway.
JoJo!
Oh, man.
How long can he last when
all he can do is run for it?
Fly, boy, and don't look back.
That's all we humans can do now.
Just try to save our skins.
240 kilometers an hour.
I don't care how perfect
that bastard may be.
This plane has got more horsepower.
I'm safe for now.
If he has any morning plans,
he'd better cancel them because
I'm in this for the long haul.
Or am I?
Two hours left.
Guess I can't give him the slip
for as long as I had thought.
You cretin.
That metal coffin of yours will
only protect you for so long.
If your plan involves landing
somewhere, I've got news for you.
The only way you'll return to
Terra Firma is in bloody chunks.
Jojo! Jojo! Do you read me?
This is Speedwagon over!
Hey, you guys missing me down there yet?
Thank goodness.
Listen, you were smart to grab that plane.
I know it's not much, but the Germans and
I will do what we can to help from here.
Do you have a map?
Yeah, found it.
Good.
Maintain radio contact, and
I'll guide you to safety.
Jackpot. All right.
First, give us your current position.
What?
Jojo, you're breaking up!
What's going on? Hey!
If you can hear me, for
the love of God, pipe up!
Yeah, clear as a bell.
How do you think this is gonna go? I mean,
we don't have a weapon or fighting
technique that'll work on cars worth a damn.
You were yelling about him
being immortal, remember?
Don't I know it!
You running away isn't ideal,
but it's all you can really do!
Hmph. Maybe not.
Looking over this map gave me an idea.
What idea?
Hey, Jojo, don't face Kars alone.
This is no time to act a hero.
He'll be too strong later.
This is the only time.
Don't do it.
I forbid you to get
yourself killed out there.
Do you hear me?
Just listen for a second.
I know Kars is the most powerful
creature on Earth at the moment.
But he was born here.
Thousands of years ago,
this planet gave him life.
And if we're lucky, it'll
take that life right back.
Take it?
But how?
What in the world do you think
will be a threat to cars? Magma.
After all, magma's the
hottest substance on Earth.
I'll drive him into the
lava at Isola di Vulcano.
Even he can't survive that! No! You can't!
You've risked your neck for
humanity more than enough, boy!
Let me and the Germans do
the heavy lifting for once!
Listen to him, Jojo! Don't be stupid!
Cars is gonna kill you!
Maybe, but I'm at the
volcano, so it's too late.
Grip diem, as they say.
Mr. Speedwagon.
No, God, not again.
Lord Joestar, his son
Jonathan, and his son George.
The men of the Joestar family
were all cut down far too soon.
Not again why do they
always have their lives
taken don't fly into
that volcano survive for
Lisa Lisa's sake listen to me Lisa Lisa is
your mother what did you
say you're breaking up
Huh?
That sounds like chewing!
Are you kidding me?
Piranhas, huh?
That's logical!
They'll eat the plane
right out from under me!
But how'd they get here?
Those feathers Coz shot before!
They turned into these damn things!
Buggeroll, no!
Don't eat the parachute!
Shoot!
You devil fish!
Oh, this is bad!
Jojo!
What's going on?
Can you even hear me? Jojo!
Please, say something!
What a moron.
You think that parachute is your salvation,
but all it does is seal your fate.
You're just a butterfly
caught in a spider's web.
Now, Jojo, time to split you asunder!
What the?
But if this is a decoy... Hmm?
Hmph!
Ah!
Hey, cars!
I'm a Joestar!
We don't go down without a fight!
You and I have got a
date with that volcano!
Don't try to weasel out!
Joosho!
Ahhhh!
Danny!
You're a lunatic!
Granny Iran, a long time ago,
you told me about my grandfather.
You said he died on the Atlantic to save
you and father from his greatest foe.
Trust me, I don't mean to be a copycat.
Maybe this is the hand my blood dealt me.
Really, now?
Do you think I can pry
myself from this foul
contraption before you try
to smash it into the ground,
you gibbering primate?
You coward!
Know that your death
won't accomplish anything!
Is...
is that a hand?
What a shame all of your
scheming and still you die here?
Damn you, Von Stroheim!
Oh.
How did you get into the plane?
When did you have time?
I wasn't sure you could
handle this battle. All alone.
Next time I should stow away in the cabin.
Proper next time, huh?
Then I give the word.
Jump out, Jojo!
Not on your life! No way!
Believe it or not, piranhas
ate my damn parachute!
Unless you want to die, jump
out of there this instant!
Please respond!
I don't care what you say!
Tell a bad joke, or call me an old man!
Let me hear your voice
one more time! I'm...
Jojo...
Stroheim, you're crazy!
I'm crazy too, but...
I admit when someone's got me beat...
That was a pretty courageous move.
You seem to be all right.
But what about Vertigo?
Please tell me cars fell into the lava.
I'm still alive.
I'll be the roundabout The words will make
you out and out You'll
spend the day your way
Calling morning, running through
the sun And in and out the valley
In and around the lake
Minds come out of the sky They stand there
One mile over We'll be there We'll see you
Two samples We'll be there You'll be too
Twenty-four We'll see you
I'll be there with you
Did you say harm on overdrive?
Who's laughing now, huh?
To purge your fears and
reign forever as God!
JoJo!
Everyone, goodbye.